<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Definition of Done-Health]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Definition of Done-Health]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/definition-of-done-health/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 14:49:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/definition-of-done-health/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 14:49:17 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chat bot for health ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/e8d02f948689500fb3c6d17a5409927b/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=367&cropwidth=617&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Faf8c5f2d-df80-4c07-b7bb-ffa8096c0dc3.jpg&x=15&y=0" title="Chat bot for health ">,<p>The way we communicate is quickly evolving. Constituents want to be able to engage with agencies anytime on any platform or device just like they do in commercial space. So how can your health and human services agency take advantage of new ways of conversing to be more responsive in providing information when people need it?</p>,<p>Many of the health and human services leaders we’ve met with recently are especially excited about how they can use&nbsp;<a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/bot-service/">chatbots</a>&nbsp;to stay connected with those they serve 24/7, while saving their teams’ time. With chatbots in place to handle commonly asked questions, service desk and case workers can focus more of their time on improving outcomes for people in your programs.</p>,<p>For instance, child welfare agencies can use <a href="http://www.medichat.co.uk/" title="">chatbots</a> to provide foster care parents important information and services for their foster care program in real time—via multiple channels such as agency websites, phone apps, texts, or even Skype or Facebook —while reducing the call burden on their teams.</p>,<p>chatbots are designed to provide text or verbal interaction with people using natural language leveraging Artificial Intelligence. People can ask a question through a conversational channel as if they were speaking with one of your social worker or call center agents—using the platform and messaging tool of their choice. That way, they can access your agency for support for common queries and tasks when and where it’s convenient for them.</p>,<p>Plus, chatbots harness machine learning so they can continually improve.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/definition-of-done-health/chat-bot-for-health/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f29fd075-11af-4d0c-bfe4-495a182aaa95</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 14:47:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>